#### Contact

919-353-5241 (Mobile) hmjackson792@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/hannah-wilson-a3044a85 (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Lifeguarding
Cpr Certified
Certified Nursing Assistant

Certifications
CCRN
ACLS
CPR - Basic Life Support

## Hannah Wilson

BSN, RN, CCRN

Morrisville, North Carolina

### Summary

I have been an ICU Nurse since 2014 when I began my career as a new grad in the MSICU at UNC Rex Healthcare. I was at UNC Rex until December of 2019. During my time there, I developed and grew in my critical thinking, communication, and leadership skills, and was surrounded by co-workers who supported and challenged me daily.

In January of this year, I began my travel nursing adventure! I currently am employed by Host Healthcare and am on my second assignment as an ICU nurse. I have learned so much during my short time as a travel nurse and am excited to see where this adventure will take me!

## Experience

Host Healthcare, Inc.
Travel Nurse
January 2020 - Present (7 months)

**UNC REX Healthcare** 

5 years 5 months

Registered Nurse

August 2014 - December 2019 (5 years 5 months)

Raleigh, NC

M/SICU

Team Lead

February 2018 - February 2019 (1 year 1 month)

Raleigh, NC

M/SICU

Camp Oak Hill Equestrian Supervisor May 2014 - July 2014 (3 months) Oxford, NC Supervised the equestrian staff and program at camp. Taught kids the basics of horseback riding.

# Performance Rehabilitation Physical Therapy Office Assistant

April 2010 - January 2014 (3 years 10 months)

Sanford, NC

I help schedule patients for their physical therapy appointments and I help the PT's keep their patients going with exercises

# Camp Oak Hill Camp Counselor

May 2012 - August 2013 (1 year 4 months)

Oxford, NC

I was in charge of a cabin of 10-20 girls each week of the summer. I also life guarded, helped with horseback riding, and helped campers with other similar activities.

## Parkview Home Health and Hospice CNA

June 2011 - June 2012 (1 year 1 month)

Sanford, NC

Performed the traditional duties of a CNA in home health settings.

Bay Breeze Seafood Restaurant Cashier and Hostess June 2009 - January 2010 (8 months) Sanford, NC

Performed the traditional duties of a hostess and cashier

#### Education

University of North Carolina at Greensboro

Bachelor of Science (BS), Nursing · (2010 - 2014)